CONTACTS

- +447442468888
- +380637173812

<u>oleksandrtkachenko202@gmail.com</u>

<u>Telegram</u>

linkedin

GitHub

Ivybridge, Devon, England

TECH SKILLS

- HTML5/CSS3/SASS
- Responsive/Adaptive design
- GITHub
- JavaScript
- React
- React Hooks
- Redux
- RTK Query
- Parcel
- AJAX
- REST API
- React Native
- Node JS
- Mongo DB
- Express
- Mongoose
- WebSockets
- TypeScript

SOFT SKILLS

- Strategic thinking
- Quick learning skills
- · Ability to work efficiently both
- individually and in a team

LANGUAGES

- English Intermediate
- Ukrainian Native
- Russian Native

OLEKSANDR TKACHENKO

JUNIOR FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

SUMMARY (portfolio-link)

I am Junior fullstack developer with a solid understanding of HTML, CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, NodeJS, React Native. I have experience working on team projects and specialize in creating visually appealing and user-friendly web applications, while also writing efficient code in JavaScript. My passion for innovation motivates me to constantly expand my skillset and explore new technologies. I am a quick learner with strong attention to detail, and I am excited to join a team where I can continue to develop both personally and professionally and make meaningful contributions to project success.

PROJECTS EXPERIENCE

• Movie-mania. GitHub [React, React hooks, JSX, REST API, AJAX]

On this website you can find the most popular movies, as well as search by title and review movie information. Role: developer.

• Bookshelf. GitHub [HTML, SASS, JS, REST API, AJAX, Parcel]

This is a website that helps you find popular books, their descriptions, and place orders at very good prices. Role: developer.

• Phopebook, GitHub [React, React hooks, Redux Toolkit, JSX]

The Phone Book application helps you create a contact book that is stored on a remote server. Role: developer.

• <u>Ice-cream.</u> <u>GitHub</u> [HTML, SASS, JS, Parcel]

Ice-company website with responsive layout, burger menu, modal window, animations, gallery with a JS library and attractive design. Role: developer.

• Webstudio, GitHub [HTML, CSS]

Webstudio website with a Multiple-page Application architecture. Role: developer.

WORK EXPERIENCE

web-developer.in.ua

April 2023-present. Junior Frontend Developer (volunteer).

Responsibilities:

• responsible for the Motivation section.

Chernihiv Scientific and Research Expert-Criminalistic Center of the Ministry of Internal Affairs of Ukraine.

2016-2022. Forensic Expert.

Responsibilities:

- Carrying out inspection and analysis of vehicles for changes in license plates.
- Preparing and presenting reports and documents related to the conducted expertise.

Achievements: conducted practical training for interns who successfully found employment after completing their internship.

Scientific and Research Expert-Criminalistic Center of the Ministry of Internal Affairs of Ukraine in Kyiv region.

2015-2016. Forensic Expert.

Responsibilities:

- Investigation of the crime scene, search for evidence of the crime.
- · Conducting trace, ballistic, and fingerprint examinations.

Achievements: helped to solve a number of crimes.

EDUCATION

IT School GoIT

2022 - 2023

Fullstack Developer

Chernihiv Polytechnic National University

2017 - 2018

Master's degree. Motor vehicle transport.

Academy of Business and Entrepreneurship

Master's degree. Enterprise economy.